princeedwardisland.ca 2016-03-14

# Copyright and Privacy | Tourism Prince Edward Island

The following statements outline the policy regarding copyright and privacy on the [www.tourismpei.com](http://www.tourismpei.com/) and related websites of the Province of PEI.

### Copyright

Unless otherwise specifically stated herein, all materials on this website, including text, photos, underlying HTML, illustrations, maps, designs, icons, audio clips, video clips, documents, products, software and all other content is either owned by the Government of Prince Edward Island, or the Government of Prince Edward Island has obtained a license to use the materials for the website.

The materials on this site are protect by the Copyright Act. Reproduction of any materials requires the advance written permission of the Government of Prince Edward Island, or the original creator, where applicable.

To request permission, contact the web content team using the website comments and suggestions form and detail your request in the comments section.

To request images please fill out the [Image Request Form](http://tourismpei.com/media/resources/photo-request-form/).

### Trademarks and Official Marks

All trademarks used and/or displayed on this website are registered or unregistered trademarks or official marks of the Government of Prince Edward Island.  For permission to use Trademarks and Official Marks please contact Island Information Service at [island@gov.pe.ca](mailto:island@gov.pe.ca).

### Privacy Statement

Tourism PEI is committed to protecting your privacy. Personal information you supply, including (but not limited to) your e-mail address, may be disclosed to authorized Tourism PEI personnel and contractors who need the information to fulfill your request (this may include performing research on behalf of Tourism PEI). Any personal information provided to us through this website and affiliated sites is collected, used and disclosed in accordance with the Prince Edward Island [Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act](http://www.gov.pe.ca/jps/FOIPPfaqs) or other applicable legislation.

The information you provide is used by Tourism PEI to serve you better, via newsletter communication, account management on tourism websites, etc. You may receive email newsletters, updates or research calls based on the interests and/or willingness to participate you've indicated. You may of course at any time opt out of these services. Access to computer data and files is secured by password coding and is controlled by the Government of Prince Edward Island.

If you do nothing during your visit but browse the website, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store only the following information about your visit:

  * The Internet domain and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web) from which you access our website;
  * the type of browser and operating system used to access our site;
  * the date and time you access our site;
  * the pages you visit; and
  * if you linked to our website from another website, the name of that website.

We use this information to help us make our site more useful to visitors - to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. We do not track or record information about individuals and their visits unless provided to us by you.

This website uses "cookies." Cookies are small amounts of information that are distributed to web browsers to assist you when you return to this site or a specific area on the site. The cookies used here retain session information when you perform searches on the site - these are removed automatically when you close your browser. Persistent cookies are also used which records your visit and logs the following information for statistical purposes - your server's address; the name of the top-level domain from which you access the Internet; the type of browser you use; the date and time you access the site; the pages you have accessed and the documents downloaded and the previous internet address from which you linked directly to the site. Persistent cookies are not retained by this site after six months.

If you have questions about this Privacy Statement or any of Tourism PEI's use of your information, please contact:

Digital Marketing Manager  
PO Box 2000  
Charlottetown, PE  
C1A 7N8  
902-368-6316

### Tourism PEI Disclaimer

Tourism PEI uses pixels, or transparent GIF files, to help manage online advertising. These GIF files are provided by our ad management partners. These files enable our partners to recognize a unique cookie on your Web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website. The cookie was placed by us, or by another advertiser who works with our partners. With cookies the information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address.

### External Websites

The government of Prince Edward Island makes no warranties, guarantees or representations about any external website it references, and it will assume no responsibility or liability for any loss or damage sustained due to any inaccuracy or misinformation found at such an external website.

Further, the government of Prince Edward Island does not guarantee that any external website referenced will be available in French, or any other language. Publications which are exempted from being translated as well as government institutions which are deemed to be exempted from the requirements of the French Language Services Act, are not required to provide communications or services in French.

### Social Media Terms of Use

Tourism PEI maintains official pages or accounts on several social media websites in order to better engage with visitors and promote awareness of our activities, events and information. Tourism PEI’s use of social media serves as an extension of its presence on the web. Social media account(s) are public and users who choose to interact with us via social media should read the terms of service and privacy policies of these third-party service providers and those of any applications you use to access them.

Social media websites used by Tourism PEI include, but are not limited to, Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, YouTube, Flickr, Pinterest, Vine, Periscope and TripAdvisor. If you submit a photo, video or other materials to Tourism PEI’s social channels or official hashtag #ExplorePEI, please note that we may re-post these materials with credit to the original poster. Personal information that you provide to Tourism PEI via social media account(s) is collected to share and re-post photos and videos, as well as to capture conversations (e.g. questions and answers, comments, “likes”, retweets, posts) between you and Tourism PEI. It may be used to respond to inquiries, or for marketing, statistical, evaluation and reporting purposes. Comments that violate Tourism PEI’s rules of engagement will be deleted.
